Well, good afternoon and welcome to the
um July 20th meeting of the public
services committee. If you are here in
the room with us, if you will make sure
that your phone is turned off on manners
mode and um if you would like to speak
to the governing body, if you would um
approach the podium, make sure the green
light is on. Um everyone will have three
minutes to speak. Um if you're under
public comment and um we would ask that
you identify what ward you are currently
living in or your address if you don't
know your ward.
Um, if you are joining us online, you
will be able to make comments if you uh
raise use the raise hand feature. And
those comments will also be limited to 3
minutes after you've identified yourself
with your ward or your street address.
And with that, we'll get started. First
item, please. Number 17, ordinance,
second reading, annexing to the city of
Cheyenne, Wyoming, land west of Roundtop
Road and south of HappyJack Road. Okay.
Staff report, please.
Chair, members of the committee, Connor
White Planning and Development
Department. Uh the item before you, it's
for an annexation. This is owner
petitioned. Um this is for property that
is adjacent to North Range Business
Park.
uh this item or this property was also
granted by the governing body an outside
user agreement for water on June 22nd.
So the city has approved uh water
connection already for the property
prior to the annexation and actually
during that uh outside user agreement
staff report and when it went through
the process staff did mention that they
would be coming in for annexation
uh just around the corner. So that is
what this is. it is the annexation for
that property.
Um again it is adjacent to uh city
limits. It is actually 60% contiguous to
city limits.
Um
uh we had the public hearing last
Monday. That was the only time that
staff has had any comments on this item.
Otherwise, there have been no other
comments from the public. uh whether it
be emails, phone calls, anything on
connect Cheyenne. With that, I am
available for any questions.
>> Okay. Are there any questions for staff?
>> Okay, we'll go out for public comment.
Any public comment?
>> Madam Chair, uh Brad Emmens, AVI agents
for the owners and applicants. Just also
wanted to point out that part of the
reason to get annexed is um so they can
combine lots and expand the North Range
Business Park. So it's under two
jurisdictions. We can't uh combine the
lots and and get them all into one. So
moving forward to to make sure we can
combine and and expand the North Range
Business Park as well. Happy to answer
any questions.
>> Okay. Thank you,
>> Madam Chair. Woman.
>> Yes, Dr. Renie.
>> Through you to Mr. Emmens. Um, first of
all, this is 30 34 and a2 acres and my
understanding is this is the area that's
being used as essentially a a
construction lot or construction
material storage lot.
>> Madam Chair, through you currently
Hansel Phelps had gone through the
county conditional use process to uh set
up a construction their construction
trailers, their parking lots to start
construction on uh the parcels to the
south and east. So, um, they do have a
conditional use with the county already.
>> And how, Madam Chairwoman, how long will
that
how long is it proposed that the
construction will take?
>> Madam Chair, through you, you know, I
don't know that I know totally. Um,
usually I would just say in general each
building, um, seems like it takes about
a year for building and I think they've
just started on the first one and I
haven't seen
>> and there are two buildings.
>> Um,
we didn't do the site plan for it, so I
don't know. I would think there would be
two buildings though. And Madam
Chairwoman, do once the construction's
completed, do they have a different
long-term plan for that lot or is it or
is there no plan at this point?
>> Madam Chair, through at this point, I
have not heard of any other plans for
it.
>> Thank you, Madam Chair.
>> Okay. Any other questions?
Okay. Any other public comment? Thank
you, Mr. Evans.
Any public comment online?
Seeing or hearing none, um I would
entertain a motion.
>> Madam Chairman, I would move to approve
on second reading.
>> Second. We have a motion by Dr. Renie, a
second by Dr. Emmens. Um is there any
discussion?
Hearing none. Dr. Renie, did you have a
question?
>> No ma'am.
>> Okay. All in favor say I.
>> I.
>> Opposed. Okay. This item will move
forward to the governing body, the next
meeting of the council. Next item,
please. Number 18, ordinance, second
reading, amending the official zoning
map of the city of Cheyenne,
establishing the zoning classification
of BP business park for land annex to
the city of Cheyenne, located west of
Roundtop Road and south of HappyJack
Road.
>> Okay. [clears throat] Uh staff report,
please.
>> Madam chair, members of the committee,
Conor Planning and Development
Department,
the item before you, like with any
annexation, we have an assigned zoning.
Need to give a property a city zone when
it gets annexed. Um, this might be the
first one though that you're seeing
where staff is actually recommending
that it just be assigned the BP zone uh
rather than having a zone change
involved. Um, the reason for that, uh,
staff did review this, uh, and go
through a few different kind of options.
Um,
but ultimately with this property, uh,
it's got BP on two out of the four
sides. Um, it is adjacent to BP zoning
already. Northr Range Business Park when
it was annexed into the city was
actually given the BP zone. The BP zone
was actually created specifically for
that annexation for North Range because
it was under a county PUD.
Secondly, um, as our applicant mentioned
when they were up here under the
annexation, this property already has
approval for industrial style use. Uh so
it's being used for construction
trailers, parking, lay down yard. Um
basically it is an industrial use
already that is permitted for the land.
So when we look at the use of the land,
uh it's already got an industrial use
that's allowed and already present. Um
to the east or not sorry to the west is
county land use. county land use. Um,
that's what this property currently is
in the county. Allows for a lot of
different uses. As the applicant
mentioned, they had to go through a
conditional use to get their current
approved use.
Um, and then to the north is an
agricultural zone in the city. Um, so
it's zoned AG, but that has a Black Hill
substation on it. Back when we were
doing assigned zoning with the
annexation of North Range Business Park,
we basically had it where we just took
the underlying county zone and gave it
the closest zone and in the county that
property was A1 or A2, one of the two.
Um, so a was the closest, but even that
a zone has pretty much an uh industrial
style use on the property. Again, with
the BP zone, it's meant to be kind of a
mix of LIHB
zoning uh and allow for industrial uses.
Being this is adjacent to BP zoning,
staff just recommends that it be
assigned the BP zone when it is annexed.
Obviously, if council doesn't agree,
then staff would recommend either any of
our light industrial or light industrial
or heavy industrial zone to give it an
industrial zone district upon
annexation. But staff would recommend
the BP zone because that is what already
exists in the area. That is what it's
adjacent to. Um, this was heard by the
planning commission and the planning
commission did recommend approval of the
assigned zoning. Uh, staff recommends
approval and I am available for any
questions.
>> Thank you. Are there any questions from
committee?
>> Okay, we'll go out for public comment.
Any public comment on this zone change?
Any public comment online?
Nope.
>> Okay. Hearing none or seeing none, um,
all in favor? Oh, sorry. I guess I would
entertain a motion first.
Chairwoman, I move to approve on second
reading.
>> Second.
>> We have a motion from Dr. Emmens and a
second by Dr. Renie. Is there any
discussion?
Hearing none. All in favor say I.
>> I.
>> Opposed? This item will move forward
with a recommendation to approve at the
next meeting of the council. Our last
item, please. Number 25 resolution
authorizing the mayor and the city clerk
to sign a final plat for A&H Park at
Sweetgrass, City of Cheyenne, Larmy
County, Wyoming, located south of East
College Drive and west of Sweet
Sweetgrass Drive. Hey, staff report.
>> Madam Chair, members of the committee,
Connor White Planning and Development
Department. The item before you is for a
final plat for um NH Park at Sweetrass.
Uh this is basically the the park uh
that we had discussions on with the PUB
amendment just a couple months ago. Uh
so with this subdivision, it is creating
a number of lots. Um
you have a uh a lot for the city park, a
second lot for the um
potential of having a private
recreational
um development
adjacent to the park. And then there is
a greenway
uh greenway lot, a lot for a small
electrical substation and then two
remainder lots uh that would be proposed
on the west side of Loving Trail that
have a sign significant amount of
easements going across them.
So with this plaid, it does dedicate
multiple different rights of way. Uh
there's East Murray Road that is getting
dedicated all the way to the west that
connects into a new dedicated loving
trail and then there is East Nation Road
as well um that is dedicated on the
south end. There is a small dedication
for Artisian as well to connect further
to the west.
Uh with the review of this plat
uh there was a couple of different items
that did come up. Um,
one of those is the exception to block
size. So, the exception to block size is
basically these are larger than typical
blocks, but this is also a residential
or not a residential, sorry,
recreational style plat. So, you are
meant to have larger blocks as it is
looking at larger lots uh for the
residential as or the recreational
aspect. Um,
the other uh couple of other things that
came up was just some technical
corrections. that still need to be made
for the plat. Um and then the major
thing that came up um and there will
probably be a discussion on as well uh
it was discussed at planning commission
is that with any plat uh it is required
by the UDC that either a plan for
installation of all necessary public and
private infrastructure be in placed and
assurance by bond or certified check
uh be provided or a development
agreement uh with or a development
agreement or other written legal
obligations.
be approved by the city. Um, basically
with any plat for the basically
construction of those roads, a plan
wasn't provided. Um so one of the
conditions that staff had placed on this
is that either the plan be provided
prior to recording of the plat uh or a
development agreement
basically be uh drafted and approved and
all of that through both planning and
development the city engineer uh and
then having to go before council for
that approval be in place prior to the
recording of the plat um through
planning commission and the discussions
planning commission uh basically did
move to approve uh the plat with uh the
exception to block size and then with
the conditions that staff had so prior
to recording of the plat that plan or uh
development agreement be in place and
then technical corrections be made but
they did request further discussion on
the timing of condition basically 2A
which is the installation
um of the necessarily the the roads
basically uh in regards to being prior
to recording or prior to building
permit.
Um so that was a discussion at planning
commission. Uh the applicant will
probably explain it more when they come
up uh that they would prefer it to be
prior to building permit that those be
in place so that they can record the
plat. Uh staff have this as being prior
to recording of the plat.
Um so planning commission just requests
that that discussion be had at council.
Um and council ultimately decide if it's
prior to recording of the plat or prior
to building permit. Um the applicant
will explain the reasoning for wanting
it to be prior to permit.
Uh but ultimately there needs to be
something in place on how these roads
are going to be built. Um again, yes,
this is a city park, but UDC does call
out that with any platting action from
any developer, they are ultimately
responsible for the construction of all
roads that are being uh clatted with
that plat.
So again, staff does recommend approval.
Planning commission did recommend
approval with the conditions. Um but
then planning commission also requested
that there be some sort of discussion on
the timing for condition 2A which is the
development agreement or having that
plan in place for construction of the
roads. Um
and again this is for
uh creating the city park at Sweetgrass
along with another recreational
uh lot for private recreational
development and then a couple of other
lots as well. With that I am available
for any questions. Any questions for
staff? Dr.
I'll
>> yield.
>> Um, thank you, Madam Chairwoman.
Can you point to
the exact area you're talking about?
>> Actually, can you just
>> Madam Chairman, I have a similar
question. I can't find lot four looking
here. And so, can you like show us where
that is? And then to follow up with my
colleague, can you tell us what the use
for the blocks one, two, three? Can you
delineate those again, please?
>> Yes, ma'am. Chair, through you. So, lot
four is up adjacent to East Murray Road.
It's probably really hard to see on a
tiny tiny map that you have, but there
is a lot four. It is public greenway. It
connects into the other greenway that we
have out in this area.
>> I found it.
>> Um, lot one would be the lot that's
dedicated as the city park, so 45 acres.
Lot three is a uh electrical substation
from Black Hills
that already exists which is up in this
corner.
Lot five and six are on the west side of
the dedication for Loving Trail. Those
are remainder lots. Those basically have
a ton of uh easements going through them
for whether it be electrical, pipeline,
gas, all of that. And then lot two,
which is the southern lot, would be the
private recreational development lot
that was discussed with the PUD
amendment.
>> Hey, Dr. Minnie.
>> Thank you. And thank you, Madam
Chairwoman, for letting me jump on that.
That's exactly the information I wanted
and I finally found lot four. Um so
madam chairman does on the
um on the exceptions or on the rec the
planning commission recommendations. I
understand that the developer has a
preferred timeline. Does our staff have
a a preferred timeline as to when those
should be considered? Madam Chair,
through you, I would have to leave that
up to the directors to determine if they
would be willing to allow it to be prior
to building permit or if we do want it
prior to plat recording. I don't know if
I can answer that specifically.
>> Okay.
Ah, perhaps engineer Cobb has an answer.
>> Madam Chair, uh through you to Dr.
Renie. Dr. Renie, I'm perfectly fine um
with delaying this. it doesn't need to
be done now. Um I think one of the
particulars that I would like to have if
we're going to do some type of agreement
is to ensure the city has no cost to
those adjacent roads because normally we
refer back to the owner, right? So we've
got basically three roadways that touch
the park. I just don't want the city or
the taxpayer responsible for those
construction items.
>> Dr. Winnie,
>> thank you. You can see my the wheels
turning, huh? I how have we handled
situations like that in the past?
Because it seems to me I mean if if our
ordinance says that the land owner is
going to pay for a portion where the
land owner that how do we get around
that or have we had developers pay for
those areas in the past? Madam Chair
through you. So when it comes to
subdivisions generally um it's generally
the developers putting in those roads
prior to even the city allowing them to
build homes.
um we deal most of the time we deal with
residential developments when that comes
up. So for instance, if you remember, we
just recently had the Harmony Valley
23rd filing uh that was a complete
residential subdivision. Basically, that
developer of that subdivision will have
to have all those streets built and in
place with all utilities and everything
prior to even being allowed to start
building homes in there. Um, and then
usually when we have, I would say, a
devel or a property owner that's
responsible for building out the road,
it's in our older parts of town where
somehow back in the day, previous to
probably any of us in here, we allowed
roads to be I know you and me. I it
could it could have been before you as
well. Um, but it was basically we didn't
have the roads built at the time of the
plat and then it was on if now that
property gets built today, they're
responsible for building out those
roads. But this is all unplatted land.
So this would basically be treated as
any plat that we've had come before this
governing body where basically the
developer who's platting it would be
responsible for those roads.
>> Madam Chairman, I I think a similar
situation I guess comes to my mind. We
have a large um what I think is
designated city open space in the middle
of Saddle Ridge and I think that
developer did all the streets around
that open space. Is that correct?
>> Madam Chair, that is correct.
>> So we're not asking for anything we
haven't expected in the past. All right.
Thank you.
>> I have a question if the committee would
um indulge me. What is the timing
difference between um at plat recording
or at permitting time? Are we talking
months, years that the street before the
street would have to be developed and
completed?
>> Madam Chair, I would you know obviously
the platting action as soon as you
approve it, they can record it. So they
that timing would be immediate. So
within a month um whereas the other
would be a much longer time frame.
>> Okay. Thank you.
Okay. It looks like we have Mr. Palma to
speak to us under public comment.
Sure.
>> Sure. Anything else?
>> Nope. I would say I'll let the applicant
kind of explain
why they would prefer to be a uh not
prior to recording and then we need to
have further discussion. I'm still
available for questions in here.
>> We'll start Mr. Palma public comment
with you.
>> Good afternoon, chair, members of the
committee. Uh Casey Palmer, Palmland
planning agent for the owner. Um,
so as staff noted, the main purpose of
this plat is to create land to be
donated. So both the public and private
recreation parcels are not they're not
to be sold. They're intended to be
donated for recreational purposes. None
of us know for sure if the indoor
fieldhouse project is a go or not, but
if this lot is created, then it could be
donated to that end user. Um the other
purpose is to um as staff noted there's
a a corn that the corner of Murray and
Avenue C there is a outofstate company
that owns that facility and the ground
under it and so it's taken us taken me
almost three years to get them
negotiated to the point that we can push
those roads through there. So that was a
huge win on our side. So this plat does
kind of memorialize that and get those
rights away pushed through. Um and then
obviously there's rights of way intended
to surround the park and so um this plat
creates those alignments and kind of
does some bookkeeping on that side to
create those. Um as as Mr. Cobb noted um
typically the the adjacent owner
develops those roads or the developer
develops those roads. park as opposed to
the saddle ridge park uh was required
with the PUD to be in between the
neighboring parcels and the proposed
development so that it could be shared
as a neighborhood park. Uh kind of like
the Kowanas Park is out east. And so um
there there's a few other reasons why it
wasn't developed at the outset of the
project, but that's one of them, right?
Those people on the west side aren't
contributing.
So there are negotiations happening on
all of the sides of this plat that that
this owner controls. So as those lands
be it the the private park residential
to the south, the residential to the
east and a potential affordable housing
project coming on the west side of love
trail. Those will be um joint
partnerships between the developer and
those new new folks that are coming in.
And so in order to donate these lands or
dedicate them to the city, they have to
be created on a plat. Um well,
technically the city can, but would
prefer not to accept them unless they're
platted. So um the idea here is to
create those parcels. The parks
department will be proceeding um in a
joint master plan with sweetgrass um
later this year on this parcel. Uh but
it we need to get it conveyed to the
parks department. So that's what this
plan does is create that. And of course
then while you're doing that establish
those surrounding rights of way. So
that's kind of the main point of this
plat. Um and I think there there are
mechanisms to construct these roads but
what we need to do first is record the
plat so that we can make those land
donations so then we can work with the
surrounding parties to get the
infrastructure extensions. There's about
7,500 ft of road, water and sewer, not
to mention power and gas that would be
part of this loop around the park. Um,
as I mentioned, there's no salailable
parcels in this
plat. So, there really there's no money
now to build any of that. So, in regards
to the question of timing,
if it's at the time of recordation, I
mean, there can be an agreement, but
that doesn't change the fact that it
can't be done until there's revenue to
do so. So, I don't think that the
condition when the condition applies
matters per se because it can only be
done once there's revenue to construct
those improvements.
That being said, um there is a larger
network plan uh that we've been working
on in terms of what improvements need to
be made and where uh extending all the
way from Fox Farm down to the south end
of Bison Business Park and Terry Ranch
Road. Um and so we're we're one piece in
all of that, but um this also plays into
that. Loving trail has been um
identified as a potential alternate
route for that. And so that's another
party that maybe since we don't have
land owners on the west side of the road
contributing um if it's a part of that
larger plan, that will that will affect
it too and also affect the timing as to
when these things happen. But um all
that being said, those are kind of the
main points that we have and why we had
asked for the the condition to be
deferred to certificate of occupancy uh
as opposed to recordation because we
really do need to create the lots so
that they can be donated. That's that's
sort of the the primary impetus of what
we're doing here. Um we're fine with all
the other conditions. There are a few
technical corrections including
extending nation to the west. Um those
are those are all fine. This landowner
does control that land. So, I don't
think that would be a problem to create
that rightaway extension. I've met with
the city engineer um and in my mind, and
I I believe he agrees with me that we we
really don't need condition 2A at all.
Um the municipal code says, I could read
it word for word, but basically um prior
to any certificant of occupancy being
issued, um off-site improvements have to
either be installed or have uh
u signed contract and bond or cash
deposit or letter of credit. So, we'll
continue to work with the city, Y dot,
leads, and the other parties in in all
this network stuff, including, you know,
our neighbors in developing those
roadways as quickly as possible. Um, I
think we could either get rid of the
condition or if you don't want to get
rid of it, we could. Um, or if our staff
would prefer it stay in, we would just
request that it be at certificate of
occupancy. So, if something's not in
place, then there needs to be a bond. If
something is in place, then everything's
good. So, hopefully, sorry to get kind
of long-winded. There's sort of a lot of
weird little pieces here. So, um, just
wanted to be complete in my explanation.
I'd be happy to take any questions.
Yeah.
>> Okay. Any questions from committee
>> for Mr. Paul?
>> Okay. Dr. Renie.
>> Thank you, Madam Chairwoman. So,
um, Mr. Cobb, your opinion and Mr. who I
can chime into. Does the
um administration prefer the 2A stay
there or is it really not needed?
>> Madam Chair, through you. Um so I mean
as the planning department we throw that
in there because it is something in the
UDC. There wasn't something provided.
Obviously if the city engineer believes
that we don't really need it and council
believes we don't need it and we can
still work all that out, that's fine.
If everybody agrees that it can be prior
to basically certificate of occupancy,
it can be changed to that as well. Um, I
don't know if I really have one way or
another as long as we do make sure it's
clear though for the record that the
city will not be responsible for the
ropes.
>> Madam Chair, I I would concur with Mr.
White in that regard. I think maybe we
do need to memorialize it in some type
of agreement in this case just because
if this ownership takes place then we
have the transfer into the city. I just
want to make it clear that the taxpayer
is not responsible for construction of
roads. Um I I guess I would back it up
even further. I think the agreement
needs to be in place before any
development action occurs out here
rather than co cuz what happens is
sometimes we've had in the past before
my time a portion of Whitney Ranch was
constructed um they started building
homes before they actually had roads in.
So we had no way to get um emergency
services to those particular locations.
So I would like if you're I if the
condition stays I'd like to say um
before development action and move on.
>> Okay. All right, Madam Chairwoman.
>> Yes, Dr.
>> And if we're going to amend chap 2A
to allow for at the time of the cert
certificate of occupancy where
have either of you come up with the
language you want in there and where you
want it.
>> Can we just
>> Does Mr. Palma have that? Somebody had
that.
>> Madam Chair, through you. Um
>> I'm guessing we would need a substitute
or something for Monday's meeting.
>> No. So madam chair through you. So these
are just conditions basically. So you
can make the motion to recommend
approval uh with staff condition 1A
2B and
>> 2B and then you can basically um modify
it so that 2A rather than being prior to
recording of the final plat be prior to
any development action
and I think that would suffice for
>> basically what we're looking for so that
it is A just moves out
>> in there. Um because then it still keeps
2B. So technical corrections still need
to be made. Uh 1 A is basically an
exception to block size that needs to be
granted.
>> So pardon me, Madam Chairwoman, but to
interrupt Mr. White. So under 2A, like
I'm going with what we have online. I
don't even see a reference to prior
prior to recording of the final plat in
2A.
>> So it's it's basically it's under two.
So two just basically says prior to
recording of final plat.
>> So that's where it would be changed
would be prior to recording
>> prior to any development action
>> any development action.
>> The only thing is we do want to keep 2B
being prior to recording of the final
plat because we want technical
corrections done before we record.
>> So if we make that amendment you guys
staff and Mr. Palmer are all comfortable
with that.
>> All right.
Thank you, Madam Chairwoman. Whenever
you
>> Okay, Dr. Evans, did you have any
questions?
>> I do. Um, thank you through you, Madam
Chairwoman. Um, Mr. Palma, so is the
developer opposed to being responsible
for the roads?
>> Uh, through you, chair. No, no, that's
typically expected. I think we all knew
that was coming. It's just because of
the unique circumstance of this land and
and this plat, it's it's not feasible to
build it today. But if we can get the
lands created, the rights away created,
I think there's a lot of work we can do
to move those construction projects
quickly forward. So,
>> thank you.
>> Thank you.
>> Any other questions committee?
>> I did have one question. Uh, does that
if we remove 2A, does that then remove
the expectation of bonding?
>> Madam Chair, through you not.
If you're removing it, I don't think it
would. If you're fully out removing it
and not changing it to being prior to
development action, I don't think it
still gets rid of the requirement. It's
just it's better to have it, I think, as
a condition so everybody knows moving
forward. Just I our staff likes to put
it this way. What if our staff [snorts]
completely changes over in the next year
and nobody remembers that that's a thing
or other departments change over or just
none of us are here? Um
how are we going to remember that that
still needs to be kind of done without
having it kind of memorialized in the
record as being a condition? Um, so I
that's again I think why um engineer
Cobb and myself would probably rather
have it be just amended to prior to
development action rather than
completely removing it.
>> Thank you. Yes, Mr. Palmer.
>> Madam Chair, um I think we could just
take condition 2A and move it into a new
condition, condition three. And the only
thing that changes about none of the
language needs to change except that it
be condition three is applicable at time
of development action
and I think that would just
>> yeah so condition one condition 2B um
and then a new condition three that just
reads exactly the same except applicable
at development action. That would be it.
I mean just to keep it simple.
>> Thank you.
>> Okay. Um, we'll go ahead and do public
comment. Any other public comment?
Don't see any from our large crowd
today. And I'm not seeing any online.
So, I would entertain a motion.
>> Madam Chairwoman, I would move to adopt
with stack recommendations one and two.
I need a second then we can amend it.
All right. So I was just going to amend
it by the half sentence following line
two. Change that to prior to any
development action.
>> Okay.
>> Is it more clear if we move if we so
madam chair through you? The only thing
about changing to to be prior to
development action then also keeps
technical corrections prior to
development action and we need that
prior to recording.
>> So you want those. Got it. Now I
understand that.
>> Yeah. If we can just move basically a to
it.
>> I would like to amend
um by
moving 2 A and renumbering that as
number three
and saying prior to any development
action and making
>> 2B
>> and removing B. So or I guess reumbering
2B as 2 A.
>> Okay.
>> Does that make sense to everybody?
Should I just be clear about this? So,
the original amendment was to approve
with staff recommendations number one
and number 2B,
not 2A. And now you are amending.
>> That works. That's Yeah, that's exactly
what I said.
>> Not really, but [laughter]
>> I second heard it. So we have a we have
an amendment to um continue to use my
understanding is one and 2B
>> and then 2 A will now become three
>> three and
>> and we'll read number 2B
>> and prior to
um
>> three will say prior to any development
action and then the wording for 2A will
fit into there. Okay.
>> Okay. Um, we'll go out for public
comment on the amendment.
Hearing or seeing that any on public
line on on Zoom?
Not seeing any.
>> Okay. We will vote on the amendment
first. Any discussion?
Dr. M, did you have a question?
>> Oh, no.
>> Okay. All in favor say I. I.
>> Opposed? Okay. The amendment passes.
We're back on the main motion. Um, any
discussion?
All in favor say I.
>> I.
>> Okay. This item will move forward with a
recommendation to approve as amended at
the next meeting of the council. With
that, we've concluded our agenda for
today and so this meeting is adjourned.